<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Argentina football team &#8211; Reframe dev Turbovote</title>
	<atom:link href="https://reframe-dev.turbovote.org/tag/argentina-football-team/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://reframe-dev.turbovote.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 06:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://reframe-dev.turbovote.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/refrme.png</url>
	<title>Argentina football team &#8211; Reframe dev Turbovote</title>
	<link>https://reframe-dev.turbovote.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Messi&#8217;s contract with Inter Miami for how many years, how much money</title>
		<link>https://reframe-dev.turbovote.org/messis-contract-with-inter-miami-for-how-many-years-how-much-money/</link>
					<comments>https://reframe-dev.turbovote.org/messis-contract-with-inter-miami-for-how-many-years-how-much-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dokinade]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 06:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina football team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/online-edu/?p=56</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lionel Messi put an end to all speculations last night Bangladesh time. In an interview with the Spanish media &#8220;El Mundo&#8221; and &#8220;Mundo Deportivo&#8221; about joining Inter Miami, the American Major League Soccer (MLS) team . Through this, Saudi Arabian club Al Hilal and Spanish club Barcelona also fell out of the race to buy [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Lionel Messi put an end to all speculations last night Bangladesh time. In an interview with the Spanish media &#8220;El Mundo&#8221; and &#8220;Mundo Deportivo&#8221; about joining Inter Miami, the American Major League Soccer (MLS) team . Through this, Saudi Arabian club Al Hilal and Spanish club Barcelona also fell out of the race to buy Messi.</p>



<p>In the last few days, Messi&#8217;s change of party did not happen! The Saudi club&#8217;s salary of more than one billion dollars did not attract Messi. If he played in Europe, he would have played only in Barca, but even that did not show the light of day, but the Argentine star has made Miami his new address. The 35-year-old Messi wants to spend more time with his family, the future of his children and playing stress-free football at the end of his career in a cheerful mood.</p>



<p>In an interview yesterday, Messi himself said, &#8220;The work of completing the contract with Inter Miami is not yet 100% finished.&#8221; Some things are still left.&#8217; However, speculations have been going on since last night about how Messi&#8217;s contract with David Beckham&#8217;s club could be. Argentinian media outlet &#8216;TYC Sports&#8217; reported that Inter Miami&#8217;s contract with Messi will be for three seasons. If you want to leave after the first two seasons, this condition will be kept in the contract. And the issue of extending the period must be based on the consent of both parties.</p>



<p>However, according to the Spanish media &#8216;Sport&#8217;, Messi has been offered a four-year contract. Another Spanish newspaper &#8220;Relevo&#8221;, however, claimed that the contract will be for two years.</p>



<p>Messi will officially join Inter Miami from July 1 at the end of his contract with PSG on June 30. The exact figure for his salary in Miami is not known. However, the Spanish media claimed that in addition to receiving a salary of 54 million dollars per season, Messi will also have the opportunity to earn from some other sectors.</p>



<p>According to the US media &#8216;The Athletic&#8217;, Messi will also earn from Apple and Adidas. Both organizations are affiliated with Major League Soccer (MLS). MLS matches are shown on Apple TV Plus. Apple and MLS have discussed giving Messi a portion of the revenue generated by showing matches to new subscribers. Apple and MLS have a contract worth 2.5 billion dollars for about 10 years. Apple announced on Tuesday that a four-part documentary series about Messi&#8217;s World Cup win will be shown on Apple TV Plus, which can be viewed via subscription.</p>



<p>German sports equipment manufacturer Adidas is the largest corporate sponsor of MLS. The company wants to share dividends with Messi from the income that Adidas will get from its involvement with MLS. According to sources via Athletic, this offer has been made to Messi. Adidas has been with the tournament since its inception in 1996. At the beginning of this year, Adidas also signed an agreement with MLS worth 83 million dollars until 2030.</p>



<p>Athletic also reported that after his playing career, Messi could become a partner in the ownership of a team in MLS, and that opportunity will be kept in the contract with Inter Miami. Los Angeles Galaxy kept such an opportunity in the contract with David Beckham and later Miami bought this former England midfielder.</p>



<p>However, since Miami&#8217;s agreement with Messi has not yet been completed, it is not possible to say for sure how much money the seven-time best player of the year in American football will earn from any sector. But it is certain, Inter Miami is going to be Messi&#8217;s new address.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://reframe-dev.turbovote.org/messis-contract-with-inter-miami-for-how-many-years-how-much-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
